<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sections on Instablog</title>
    <link>http://cdeck3r.com/instablog/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sections on Instablog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://cdeck3r.com/instablog/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>MVP</title>
      <link>http://cdeck3r.com/instablog/post/mvp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cdeck3r.com/instablog/post/mvp/</guid>
      <description>The minimum viable product creates the initial value.
All Instagram posts of a selected single date shall be listed in a day&amp;rsquo;s blog post on DramaLamas.tours. The blog post shall display the correct date. It shall contain for each Instagram post at least
 caption date and time image link from the image to Instagram post  Note: Instablog sources a profile&amp;rsquo;s feed. Since the Instagram website shows only up 12 recent posts in a feed, the blog post is limited to those recent posts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Components</title>
      <link>http://cdeck3r.com/instablog/post/components/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 19:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cdeck3r.com/instablog/post/components/</guid>
      <description>instacrawler Instacrawler collects URLs of posts from an Instagram&amp;rsquo;s profile feed. It identifies posts by their short code - an alphanumeric string, such as BhRpkfqgnsf.
The software component consists of two parts.
 instacrawler.sh Defines the profile URL and the file storing posts&amp;rsquo; shortcodes as .csv file. Afterwards, it calls the python script to do the work. instacrawler.py Downloads the profile website, extracts the shortcodes and stores them in .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Concept</title>
      <link>http://cdeck3r.com/instablog/post/design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 19:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cdeck3r.com/instablog/post/design/</guid>
      <description>This is a brief design sketch of Instablog&amp;rsquo;s components.
 instacrawler: collect URLs from Instagram&amp;rsquo;s profile instapost: download a single Instagram post&amp;rsquo;s data blogpost: create a blogpost from all Instagram posts of a single day  The DramaLamas blog is a jekyll website hosted on GitHub. Updating the blog is a git commit activity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://cdeck3r.com/instablog/post/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cdeck3r.com/instablog/post/about/</guid>
      <description>In August 2019, the team DramaLamas will take part in the charity rallye BALKAN EXPRESS RALLY. We want to document our trip using Instagram as well as on our blog.
Important websites
 Team website DramaLamas: dramalamas.tours Team&amp;rsquo;s Instagram profile: dramalamas.tours2019  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conclusion</title>
      <link>http://cdeck3r.com/instablog/post/conclusion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cdeck3r.com/instablog/post/conclusion/</guid>
      <description>This section concludes the project.
Summary The list below displays the achieved objectives:
&amp;hellip; &amp;hellip;  Conclusion Instablog autonomously monitors our Instagram profile for new posts and creates a blog post containing on instagram post from a single day.
Final Note I took this exercise as an test case how fast I develop a small end-to-end software. In particular, this encompasses the use of Docker, Makefile, various scripting languages, version control, parallel documentation and many other development activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Definition</title>
      <link>http://cdeck3r.com/instablog/post/project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cdeck3r.com/instablog/post/project/</guid>
      <description>Existing solutions sharing instagram posts within a blog explicitly embedd an post URL. This is a manual effort one has to do for every new instagram post entry. The Instagram JavaScript plugin, Instafeed.js, utilizes Instagram&amp;rsquo;s API and retrieves new posts filtered by a user-defined function. As a result, a single blog post embedding this javascript would display a large list of Instagram post. However, it is unclear how a daily blog is generated which only contains the posts from that day.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>